=== Linnya Network | Live Chat ===
Contributors: Linnya Technology, Inc.
Tags: Linnya Network, linnya network, Linnya Network Live Chat, linnya network live chat, linnya, linya, linia, linnyachat, liniachat, linia webchat, 
linnya network web livechat online, attendance, comment, website, roi, SAC, contact, form, ecommerce, e-commerce, store, sales, sell, shop, downloadable, 
downloads, paypal, playstore, google, materialdesign, materialup, materialdesignicons, saas, Chat, chat for website, chat online, chat software, click desk, 
clickdesk, contact plugin, contact us, customer support, живой сайт, живосайт, free chat, IM Chat, jivochat, jivosite, live chat, live chat inc, live chat services, 
live chat software, live chatting, live help, live support, live web chat, livechat, olark, online chat, online support, php live chat, snapengage, support software, 
Website Chat, WordPress chat, wordpress live chat, wordpress live chat plugin, zendesk, Zopim, Zopim live chat, zopim, ionic, firebase, firebase chat, angular, 
angularjs, app, android, android chat, push notifications, push, push notification

Requires at least: 4.0.0
Tested up to: 4.7.1
Stable tag: 4.3
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

A powerful new way to build trust. Install Linnya Network Live Chat today and start talking to your website visitors in real-time.

== Description ==

Anytime, Anywhere. Talk to your visitors in real-time, increase your sales, engage more people and change your business for better! 
Linnya Network Live Chat is a powerful tool carefully made by attendance and communication experts who really understand your daily matters.

Contact forms, endless phone calls, and boring emails are going to be extinct. It's time for you to change your attendance system for 
something bigger, based on effectiveness and humanity.

P.s.:No credit card required!

= We're on betta! =

We're running our betta version right now (and accepting help from testers!).Every new account comes with:
* Unlimmited Chats,
* Unlimmited Attendances,
* Unlimmited Devices,
* Unlimmited Histories,
* Unlimmited Visitors to track,
* Unlimmited Locations,
* Unlimmited Uploads/Downloads,
* Unlimmited Sections,
* Unlimmited Offline Messages,
* Unlimited Invites,
* And much more!

= Peolpe first! =

Engage more people using an app made by communication experts who understand you.

= Science & Expertise =

The effectiveness of Engineering, Automation, and Web Development knowledge united with only one goal: to build the best Live Chat for websites ever made.

= Tracking Visitors =

Do your best to help them by seeing their open pages and tabs in real-time.

= View their Location =

Country, City, and Region. Know everything about your visitors' main locations.

= Access Histories =

If the visitor is comming back, try using dinamic histories to improve the attendance.

= Receive messages even if you are Offline = 

You'll never lose a chance again. If the visitor has question but you're not online, an intuitive 
email will be sent to you with his/her message.

= Check out our Stack =

To the wise Developers out there: these are the key technologies that allow us to innovate and build Linnya Network in order to deliver an outstanding performance.
[Firebase](http://firebase.google.com), [Angularjs.org](http://angularjs.org), [Amazon Web Services](http://aws.amazon.com), [NodeJS](http://nodejs.org), [ionic] (http://ionic.io/).

== Installation ==

Get started in less than 5 minutes.You can easily inject the code, or integrate the App by installing our plugin for WordPress.

1. Download, Install, and Activate the plugin in your WordPress theme,
2. Go to the Linnya section at the left side, Sign in, or Create a new Account (make sure to use a valid e-mail address),
3. Once logged in, set up the Live Chat widget,
4. On your smartphone, go to the PlayStore, download the app and sign-in.
5. That's it!

Start talking to your visitors in real-time and turn them into paying customers!

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

= Do I need to have an account previously to install this mighty Plugin? =

No, you don't. But there's no problem if you already have an account. If you are moving your full html/css website to a WordPress theme, 
just go ahead. Nothing will be lost.

= Is it free? =

Yes, it is! We're running our betta version right now (and accepting help from testers!).Every new account comes with:
* Unlimited Chats,
* Unlimited Attendances,
* Unlimited Devices,
* Unlimited Histories,
* Unlimited Visitors to track,
* Unlimited Locations,
* Unlimited Uploads/Downloads,
* Unlimited Sections,
* Unlimmited Offline Messages,
* Unlimited Invites,
* And much more!

P.s.:No credit card required!

Click [here](http://linnya.com/#tester) to understand how you can grow with us!

= Can I use multiple devices with only one sign-in information? =

Yes, you can! There's no multiple agents system in this very version, so we've decided to let you sign in as many times as you want it in this betta version.

== Screenshots ==

1. Type Naturally with your visitors, as you do with your best friends.
2. Follow your personal attendance stats quickly at the "Now" screen.
3. Track what your visitors are doing before inviting them.
4. The Fresh new Widget provides meaniful interaction.
5. Easy to use.
6. Less than 5 minutes to success.
7. We're on beta. Log-in in multple devices while it's free!.
8. Don't have the app yet? Get an account traditionally on our website...
9. ...Or into this WordPress plugin.
10. Login screen on the plugin.
11. Quickly get started. 


== Changelog ==

= 0.1.0 =
* Linnya Network gets its first Plugin for WordPress.
